Gabriela Aguilar – Junior Frontend Developer

Bogotá, Colombia | +573133207188 | contacto.gariela.aguilar@gmail.com | Portfolio

PROFILE

I am a web developer with more than 3 years of experience in creating dynamic and functional websites. I have an Advanced Technical Diploma in Computer Science, which has given me a solid base to specialize in technologies such as WordPress, React, Next.js, CSS, Tailwind, TypeScript, Photoshop, and Figma. With an intermediate level of English and a focus on continuous learning, I keep myself updated with the latest technological trends, always looking to offer optimized solutions and exceed the expectations of my clients.

Technologies and Tools

React.js | Atomic Design | Wordpress | Elementor | Webmaster | Figma | BEM Methodology | Next js |
Photoshop | Tailwind

WORK EXPERIENCE

Freelance Web Development.

Jan de 2022 - present.

- Created websites using WordPres Created websites using WordPress.
- Developed mockups using Figma and Photoshop.

Dilo Club, Costa Rica

Dec 2023 - Mar 2024.

• Developed an informative website for the academy, creating a complete brand from logo design to website implementation.

The Pole Garage, Costa Rica

Aug 2023 - Mar 2024

- Web Development: Created an informative website for the academy (adricapon.com), from logo design to full website implementation.
- Content Management: Designed images and created content for social media, boosting the academy's online presence.
- Customer Service: Responsible for customer service, handling inquiries and providing efficient support to customers.

EDUCATION

Advanced Technical Diploma in Computer Science. Instituto Universitario de Tecnología 'Antonio Ricarte'. Jan 2019 – Feb 2021

LANGUAGES

- Spanish Native
- English B2

INTERESTS: Python, AI, Machine Learning, Development of themes and plugins for WordPress.